<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>oss on hotchemi.github.io</title><link>/tags/oss/</link><description>Recent content in oss on hotchemi.github.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-jp</language><copyright>Copyright (c) 2020, Shintaro Katafuchi; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/oss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PermissionsDispatcher 4.x: A bunch of stuff</title><link>/post/pd4.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/pd4.0/</guid><description>From July of this year we’ve been adding/removing a bunch of stuff to/from PermissionsDispatcher 4.x(the latest is 4.2.0 for now). I’m personally honored that there’re no changes which break backward API compatibility at all, but some of the changes are not trivial and supposed to be recognized to let you build a reliable and substantial runtime permissions grant flow in your application. In this article I’ll go through some significant changelog topics respectively in minutes.</description></item><item><title>A polite way to open a bug report</title><link>/post/polite-way-to-open-a-bug-report/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/polite-way-to-open-a-bug-report/</guid><description>I assume that as your GitHub repository becomes popular you’ll get more and more issues especially bug repot from unexpected angle. And the opposite is true, presumably you’ve opened several reports to libraries or tools that you use as you’ve been becoming being active as an open source enthusiast.
In this context what I wanna note is that opening a bug report roughly and innocently may consume project maintainer’s precious time, and even irritate them.</description></item><item><title>Joining Quipper</title><link>/post/joining-quipper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/joining-quipper/</guid><description>※ Japanese version is here.
I’m so happy to announce that today is my first day at Quipper as an Android developer.
Actually Quipper became a member of Recruit Group last year, so it’s not a career change, fortunately :-)
Motivation I had involved in the development of JyukenSapuri, but it was decided that JyukenSapuri is going to shut down and launch bland-new product, StudySapuri.
In other words…I was kinda laid off!</description></item></channel></rss>