<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tags on hotchemi.github.io</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/tags/</link><description>Recent content in Tags on hotchemi.github.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-jp</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hotchemi.github.io/tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>「美の構成学 バウハウスからフラクタルまで」を読んだ</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/synthesiology_of_beauty/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/synthesiology_of_beauty/</guid><description>Designputというpodcastで美の構成学 バウハウスからフラクタルまでという本が取り上げられていて面白かったので読んでみた。ざっくり</description></item><item><title>Meeting Etiquette</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/meeting-etiquette/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/meeting-etiquette/</guid><description>If your company is growing fast and could hire loads of employees you might have felt like &amp;ldquo;why there are such many dreadful meetings that I have got to attend?&amp;rdquo;.
To be honest I deem it&amp;rsquo;s kind of a &amp;ldquo;passage rite&amp;rdquo; and inevitable to some extent, but at least I&amp;rsquo;m sure we can mitigate the issue by making each meeting productive and on-time as much as we can. Here are some examples I usually do when facilitating a meeting(disclaimer: of course not always especially when I&amp;rsquo;m busy).</description></item><item><title>Measure What Mattersを読んだ</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/measure-what-matters/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/measure-what-matters/</guid><description>会社で推奨されていたMeasure What Matters（メジャー・ホワット・マターズ） 伝説のベンチャー投資家がGoogleに教えた成功手法 OKR</description></item><item><title>自転車通勤を始めた</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/bicycle-commuting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/bicycle-commuting/</guid><description>今働いている会社は自転車通勤が許可されていて、最近会社からそこそこ近い場所に引っ越したので自転車通勤を始めてみた。 通勤時間は20分強で、電車</description></item><item><title>最近聴いているpodcast</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/recent_subscribing_podcasts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/recent_subscribing_podcasts/</guid><description>自分は基本的にpodcastのヘビーリスナーで常に12~16個くらいの番組をsubscribeしている。 あまり新しい番組を積極的に探しに行か</description></item><item><title>2020年の始まりとpodcastの終りについて</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/2020_and_end_of_the_podcast/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/2020_and_end_of_the_podcast/</guid><description>特別意識していたわけではなかったのだけど、色々重なった結果2019年は勉強会や発表の場に一切顔を出さずオンラインでの発信もほぼしなかった。こ</description></item><item><title>PermissionsDispatcher 4.x: A bunch of stuff</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/pd4.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/pd4.0/</guid><description>From July of this year we’ve been adding/removing a bunch of stuff to/from PermissionsDispatcher 4.x(the latest is 4.2.0 for now). I’m personally honored that there’re no changes which break backward API compatibility at all, but some of the changes are not trivial and supposed to be recognized to let you build a reliable and substantial runtime permissions grant flow in your application. In this article I’ll go through some significant changelog topics respectively in minutes.</description></item><item><title>PermissionsDispatcherのプロダクトマネジメント</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/pd_pm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/pd_pm/</guid><description>ちょっと前にpmconf 2017があったり最近仕事で若干プロダクトやらプロジェクトマネジメントっぽい事にもクビを突っ込んでいる中で普段OSS</description></item><item><title>A polite way to open a bug report</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/polite-way-to-open-a-bug-report/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/polite-way-to-open-a-bug-report/</guid><description>I assume that as your GitHub repository becomes popular you’ll get more and more issues especially bug repot from unexpected angle. And the opposite is true, presumably you’ve opened several reports to libraries or tools that you use as you’ve been becoming being active as an open source enthusiast.
In this context what I wanna note is that opening a bug report roughly and innocently may consume project maintainer’s precious time, and even irritate them.</description></item><item><title>Joining Quipper</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/joining-quipper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/joining-quipper/</guid><description>※ Japanese version is here.
I’m so happy to announce that today is my first day at Quipper as an Android developer.
Actually Quipper became a member of Recruit Group last year, so it’s not a career change, fortunately :-)
Motivation I had involved in the development of JyukenSapuri, but it was decided that JyukenSapuri is going to shut down and launch bland-new product, StudySapuri.
In other words…I was kinda laid off!</description></item><item><title>DroidKaigi 2016</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/droidkaigi2016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/droidkaigi2016/</guid><description>From 2/18/2016 to 2/19/2016, there was one Android conference which is called DroidKaigi in Tokyo. Say, why am I writing such a thing? Because I’m one of the member of DroidKaigi and I definitely want to tell you about its awesomeness. And I know some guys will post a Japanese article soon, so I’m going to try to explain it in English:) Talks and Speakers I</description></item><item><title>Droidcon Krakow 2015</title><link>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/droidkcon_krakow_2015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hotchemi.github.io/post/droidkcon_krakow_2015/</guid><description>From 12/4 to 12/6, there was a Droidcon at Krakow, Poland and I joined it.
May be Krakow isn’t famous in Japan, but I heard it’s kinda like Kyoto, historic and distinctive city in Poland.
The conference was really awesome and I guess half of speakers came from out side of Poland(at least Germany, Italy, France, US, Turkey, Ukraine and Japan!). and sponsors were also global, SoundCloud from Berlin, Genymobile from Paris and many other.</description></item></channel></rss>